# Giovanni Nunez

## Software Quality Assurance and front-end intranet developer at Apple

Austin, TX - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Giovanni-Nunez/01b9db69d1d0b435

I develop and test web-based applications, and internal sites, at Apple.

My testing is a combination of manual ad-hoc and automated testing. I create functional and presentational front-end web-apps using ES6, HTML 5/ React, CSS3 / SASS, and Node JS.

I have worked on multiple projects at Apple, such as, Apple's Mac operating system, Apple's Photos for Mac, Apple's Support application for iOS, iCloud integration, and Internal corporate tools.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Software Quality Assurance**

Apple - Austin, TX - June 2016 to Present

Black Box testing of functional and non-functional behaviors, leveraging scripts in Javascript, AppleScript, and shell for more efficient manual testing.

Creation and maintenance of web-apps using multiple technologies: JavaScript, AppleScript, shell, and frameworks such as Github's Electron on the Node.js runtime.

## **Real-Time Operations, Apple Inc**

Apple inc - Austin, TX - 2015 to June 2016

Intranet Web Developer, serving content for over 15,000+ employees across the AMR, EMEA, and APAC regions, through the use of the JIVE platform.

Identified problems and implemented real time scheduling strategies to support AppleCare's performance. The analyst group monitors over 15,000+ employees for time adherence.

#### QA Software Engineer

Apple Inc - Cupertino, CA - 2014 to 2014

Quality assurance Engineer for the highly anticipated Photos application.

Develop, design, and execute testing for product validation. Black Box testing of functional and non-functional behaviors, and documentation of any software regression.

Creation of simple Javascript and shell scripts for faster and efficient testing.

# **Apple Certified Technician**

Apple Inc - Houston, TX - 2012 to 2014

Apple Certified Mac Technician for Apple hardware and software.

Market trainer for the Houston flagship Apple Store. Execute and facilitate all training for new, and at the time, 142 current employees.

### **Small Business Banker**

Personal Banker, Wells Fargo Co - Houston, TX - 2011 to 2012

Focus on acquiring small business accounts and account relationship management. Daily analysis of client accounts, in order to proactively contact customers and provide recommendations. Supervision of 5 bank tellers and their daily performance.

# **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor of Science (B.S) - Cum Laude in Computer Science

UNIVERSITY OF HOUSTON - Houston, TX 2014 to 2016

# Associate of Science in Pre-Engineering

HOUSTON COMMUNITY COLLEGE - Houston, TX 2009 to 2011

# **SKILLS**

Web Design (3 years), CSS (3 years), HTML 5 (3 years), Javascript (3 years), JQuery (3 years), QA (3 years), Quality Assurance (3 years), Spanish (10+ years), Testing (3 years), User Experience (2 years), React (1 year)

#### **LINKS**

http://gnunez.xyz

### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

### **SKILLS**

#### Software:

Web Authoring tools: Adobe Dreamweaver, Adobe Brackets, Coda, Sublime and more eWFM, Citrix Management software, Espresso, FileMaker and FileMaker Pro Radar, Microsoft Office Suite, iWork Certified, Aperture Certified, Adobe Photoshop and other Creative Suite applications.

Programing Experience / Scripting:

AppleScript, SQL, PHP and understanding of Object Oriented Programing Front-End Web: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SASS, Glt, React

System Knowledge:

Apple Mac OS X, Apple iOS, Linux, understanding of Unix and Terminal

Verbal and Written proficiency in:

Spanish, and English